Our secret that you can't reveal
The truth that no one can know
Our inseparable pair that shares a false sympathy
Beautiful and elegant, yet deceitful are these flowers
Resembling you, these Dahlias flowers
Everything is between the two of us
Our sweet, deceptive dance
Pain
[Pain] Give it to me
A feeling more genuine than love
Your punishment
I need it from you
So we can stay together
Tangled up in you, you, you, you,
you, you, you
oo I am so attached to you
You know that I'll never leave you
Unapologetic
[Unapologetic] love
Tumbling down, down, down, down, down, down,
down, down, down, down, down
Falling [down]
Just two chained together
together, in paradise
Wound [and scar]
[Wound] Me
I want you to leave a mark
You're the only one I want
To crave me back
No one will ever understand what we are
The more your hatred grows for me
I feel the invisible chains dig deeper into me
I'm a powerless flower plucked by you
My nectar giving off the scent of my tears
You shouldn't violate me
My alluring red fruit
Pain
[Pain] Give it all to me
It feels more genuine than love from you
Your punishment
Give it to me
So that we'll be bound forever
Tangled up in you, you, you, you,
you, you, you, you
Every time we hold each other
You know that I'll never leave you
Entangled in love
Tumbling down, down, down, down, down, down,
down, down, down, down, down
Close your eyes
Manipulated by lies to save our final paradise
No one can understand everything we've gone through
The more your hatred grows for me
The stronger the hatred, the safer I feel
I'll become whatever you want me to be
Then maybe, someday
I'll be able to love you
Emptiness and Isolation
False [Self-delusional] Sympathy