The secret that you can't reveal
誰にも 言えない 秘密のこと
The truth that no one can know
誰にも 言わない ホントのこと
Our inseparable pair shares a false sympathy
どこにもいけない二人の噓シンパシー
Beautiful and elegant, yet betraying are these flowers
華麗で 優雅で 裏切る花
Closely resembling you are these Dahlias flowers
誰かに よく似た ダリアの花
Everything is about our sweet, deceptive dance
すべては ふたりの
Give me pain
A feeling more genuine than love
Give me your punishment
So we can stay together
Tangled up in you, you, you, you,
you, you, you
oo so that I can't move
You know that I’ll never leave you
Our entwined love
Tumbling down, down, down, down, down, down,
down, down, down, down, down
Falling down
A paradise for two chained together
Give me a wound
I want you to leave a mark
You're the only one I want
To keep wanting me too
A truth about us that no one knows
The growing hatred you have for me
I feel invisible chains digging into me
Helpless flowers plucked by you
Their nectar giving off the scent of tears
They shouldn't be touched, with their red enticing fruit
Give me pain
A feeling more genuine than love
Give me your punishment
So we can stay together
Tangled up in you, you, you, you,
you, you, you, you
Every time we hold each other
You know that I’ll never leave you
Entangled in love
Tumbling down, down, down, down, down, down,
down, down, down, down, down
Close your eyes
Manipulating lies to have our final paradise
A truth about us that no one knows
The growing hatred you have for me
It gives me unconditional comfort no matter where you go
I'll become the version of myself that was desired by others
I wonder if then someday I can love again
Simple and lonely in this self-delusional sympathy
Pain. Give it to me
痛み 与えて
Pain
痛み
[Pain] Give it to me
与えて
Our entwined love
ほどけない 愛
Our entwined
ほどけない
[Our entwined] love
愛